korada.com 2017-12-29

# 

### **www.korada.com**

Welcomes you. We value your privacy, and want you to know what information we collect and what we do with it.

**Information Collected by korada.com**  
You can visit/surf korada.com without providing any personal information. However, if you choose to avail of certain services on our website, you shall be required to provide certain information for the registration and/or access to such services/web pages. Such information may include, without limitation, your name, email address, contact address, mobile/telephone number(s), sex, age, occupation, interests, financial information, content, IP address, standard web log information and such other information as may be required for your interaction with the services.

**Information Provided to korada.com**  
korada.com features certain areas where we ask you to provide information to us.

**Communications with Us**  
We have features where you can submit information to us (such as when contact us, Advertising with us, with a question or problem related to the service). We will retain your emails and other information you submit to us for our internal purposes, and to help us to serve you better.

**Automatic Data Collection**

Cookies   
We use a software technology called “cookies” for several purposes, depending on the type of cookie employed. Within korada.com, we use what are commonly called “session” cookies, meaning that they only last as long as you are online. We use these cookies to identify you as a valid subscriber so that we can deliver music to you, to ensure that no one else can sign on simultaneously with your account from another computer and to help us personalize your service experience based on your registration preferences (such as genre). We may also use session cookies to help us facilitate any promotions or surveys that we provide. As part of the sign-in process, we may also use what are commonly called “persistent” cookies which stay with you after your session is over and you are offline. We only use these cookies in connection with a sign-in feature that allows you to save your member name and password so that the next time you sign in, these fields will be pre populated for you. This cookie is only offered in conjunction with certain Affiliate Sites that choose to make it available and it can only be activated if you select that option during your sign-in. If you select this option you can always deselect it each time you sign-in.

Others  
In order to personalize our service for your enjoyment and to monitor and improve the performance of our technology, we do collect/capture other data such as a member’s searches (such as their search criteria and results). For our internal purposes, we gather information such as date, time, connection speed and IP address of all visitors to our site. We keep this information simply for our internal security audit log, trend analysis, and system administration.

**Third Party Advertising & Third Party Cookies **  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

**With whom we share your information**   
We do not share your personally identifiable information with other companies, apart from those acting as our agents in providing our service to you, all of which agree to use it only for that purpose and to keep the information secure and confidential. Also, entities into which our company is merged, or to which our assets, site or operations have been transferred, will be able to use your personal information under the terms of this privacy policy. We will also disclose information we maintain when required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena or other legal obligation, in response to a law enforcement agency’s request, or in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property. You should also be aware that courts of equity, such as U.S. Bankruptcy Courts, may have the authority under certain circumstances to permit your information to be shared or transferred to third parties without your permission. We may share (provide and receive) with others certain aggregate service information, which is not personally identifiable. This information may include usage and demographic data, but it will not include personal information (such as your email address). We may use aggregate demographic information about our audience in order to improve our service, for marketing purposes and/or industry reporting purposes.

**Links **  
We may display links to other sites within korada.com. We are not responsible for those other sites, their privacy policies or how they treat information about their members. We advise you to check their privacy policies to find out how they are treating your personal information.

**Downloads **  
We do link to other web sites which might support downloads. We are not responsible for the downloadable materials that are present in these websites. We are also not responsible for the legalities and privacy policy binding the downloadable materials of these websites. We are also not responsible for the legalities and privacy policy binding these downloads in the websites that our visitors refer to in our forums and discussions. Downloads referred to in this privacy policy can be videos, images, software, games and any application files.

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by [these companies.](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioural advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, [you can visit.](http://networkadvertising.org./)

**Changes in this Privacy Statement**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement and such other places we deem appropriate so that you are updated about the manner we collect information, what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
